

Pramote Supnoi

Full-stack developer

- /pramotesupnoi
- in /in/pramote-supnoi
- +6695-169-9021

About me

Hello, I'm Pramote Supnoi. You can call me James. I'm a freelance software developer with 5 years experience living in Thailand. I can develop variety kind of software such as web app, AR/VR app, game, cross platform mobile app, rest api. I believe in efficiency and clean code. If you have any questions, feel free to contact me anytime! my contact information is inside this page.

Education

2012 - 2016

Bachelor of science Information Technology (Software development) GPA 3.45

at Udon Thani Rajabhat University

Experiences

May 2015 - July 2015 Internship student

@AT Creative Solution Co.,Ltd.

May 2017 - Oct 2019

Full stack developer

@Softcare Co.,Ltd.

Oct 2019 - Oct 2020

Oct 2020 - Present

AR/VR developer

@VVR Asia Co.,Ltd.

Full stack, AR/VR developer

@Freelancer

Professional skills

JS JavaScript

React, JQuery

C# .Net

Windows form app

Python FastAPI

HTML

Unity3D

Game, AR/VR

DBMS

SQL server, MySql, Firebase, MongoDB

Additional skills

Photoshop

MS Office

Drawing

E CSS

PHP

</>

Certifications and awards

- Microsoft Offce Certification 2014 at Khon Kaen University
- Bronze medal certification in Mathematical ability creative contest using The Geometer's Sketchpad 2010 at Satrirachinuthit School
- at Santapon college

Second place in Microsoft Power Point competition 2009

at Udon Thani Rajabhat University

Second place in Microsoft Word competition 2010

Activities

- Participated in a National Software Contest (NSC) 17th Final Round 2015 at Fasion Island Shopping Mall, Bangkok
- Participated in a National Software Contest (NSC) 18th Final Round 2016 at Mahisorn Hall, Siam Commercial Bank PCL., Head Office. Bangkok
- at Udon Thani Rajabhat Univerisity

Lecturer about How to create game with Unity3D 2015

Lecturer about How to create game with Unity3D 2016

at Udon Thani Rajabhat Univerisity

at Nakhon Ratchasima Rajabhat Univerisity

at Udon Thani Rajabhat Univerisity

Lecturer about How to create game with Unity3D 2020

Lecturer about How to create game with Unity3D 2021

Lecturer about How to create mobile game with Unity3D 2016

at Udon Thani Rajabhat Univerisity



Accomplishments

- Thailand's Mental Health Center #8 : Mental health assessment system
- Hintang village's E-Commerce website

Gift Angel Radio radio station website

- Udon Thani Rajabhat University Teacher evaluation system
- Flyflow Studio Gym & Fitness membership system

Reference

Teacher

+6689-715-6151

khwanchai.s@gmail.com

Mr.Khwanchai Suksaen

